University of Arizona Athletics Collection 1913-2011
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Papers of Charles Tribolet, 1949-1975; Series VIII:
  - NCAA; CABMA, Dues Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - NCAA; CABMA, Officers Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 101, Folder 19)
  - NCAA; CABMA, Dues Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 101, Folder 20)
  - NCAA; Baseball, 1958-1959 (Box 101, Folder 21)
  - NCAA; Baseball, 1957-1958 (Box 101, Folder 22)
  - NCAA; Baseball, 1956-1957 (Box 101, Folder 23)
  - NCAA; CABMA, 1958-1959 (Box 101, Folder 24)
  - NCAA; CABMA, 1956-1961 (Box 101, Folder 25)
  - NCAA; CABMA, 1962-1963 (Box 101, Folder 26)
  - NCAA; CABMA, 1956-1961 (Box 101, Folder 27)
  - NCAA; CABMA, 1960-1962 (Box 101, Folder 28)
  - NCAA; CABMA, 1972-1974 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - NCAA; CABMA, 1974-1975 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence; A, 1959-1970 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence; B, 1958-1968 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence; C, 1958-1970 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence; D, 1957-1967 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence; E, 1960 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence; F, 1959-1967 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence; G, 1960-1969 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence; H, 1957-1970 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence; I, 1958-1960 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence; J, 1968 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence; K, 1959-1969 (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence; L, 1959-1966 (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence; M, 1958-1969 (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence; N, 1960-1964 (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence; O, 1960-1966 (Box 102, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence; P, 1958-1968 (Box 102, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence; R, 1958-1968 (Box 102, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence; S, 1959-1969 (Box 102, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence; T, 1958-1966 (Box 102, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence; V, 1959-1960 (Box 102, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence; W, 1957-1970 (Box 102, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence; X, Y, Z, 1957-1964 (Box 102, Folder 24)
  - ASUA Photo Service, 1964-1974 (Box 102, Folder 25)
  - ASUA Photo Service, 1958-1960 (Box 102, Folder 26)
  - ASUA Photo Service, 1961-1962 (Box 102, Folder 27)
  - ASUA Photo Service, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 28)
  - ASUA Photo Service, 1963-1964 (Box 102, Folder 29)
  - ASUA Photo Service, 1964-1965 (Box 102, Folder 30)
  - Photo Division, 1949-1961 (Box 102, Folder 31)
  - ASUA Photo Service, 1966-1968 (Box 102, Folder 32)
  - ASUA Photo Service, 1966-1970 (Box 102, Folder 33)
  - ASUA Photo Service, 1963-1973 (Box 102, Folder 34)
  - ASUA Photo Service, 1971-1972 (Box 102, Folder 35)
  - Home Basketball Games, December, 1953-1954 (Box 102, Folder 36)
  - Home Basketball Games, January, 1954 (Box 102, Folder 37)
  - Home Basketball Games, February, 1953-1954 (Box 102, Folder 38)
  - Basketball, Eastern Trip, 1953-1954 (Box 102, Folder 39)
  - Basketball, Border Conference Trip, 1953-1954 (Box 102, Folder 40)
  - Freshman Basketball, 1953-1954 (Box 102, Folder 41)
  - Basketball, 1953-1954 (Box 102, Folder 42)
  - Bills and Correspondence; Arizona Wildcat, 1957 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Bills and Correspondence; Kitty Kat, 1956-1960 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Bills and Correspondence; Arizona Wildcat, 1959-1960 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Bills and Correspondence; Arizona Wildcat, 1958-1959 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Bills and Correspondence; Desert, 1956-1960 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Bills and Correspondence; Desert, 1958 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Bills and Correspondence; Desert, 1958-1959 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Bills and Correspondence; Desert, 1959-1961 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Student Handbook, 1957-1959 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Associated Women Students, undated (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - UA Band, 1958-1960 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - UA Orchestra, 1956 (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - UA Glee Club, 1957-1958 (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - Livestock Judging, 1956-1958 (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - UA Intercollegiate Rodeo, 1951, 1956 (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - UA Intercollegiate Rodeo, 1955-1958 (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - UA Intercollegiate Rodeo, 1958-1959 (Box 103, Folder 17)
  - UA Intercollegiate Rodeo, 1956-1960 (Box 103, Folder 18)
  - Pacific Forensic League, 1957 (Box 103, Folder 19)
  - Reserve Account, 1957, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 20)
  - ASUA Assemblies Committee Nite Club Event, 1959-1960 (Box 103, Folder 21)
  - Community Service Committee, 1958-1960 (Box 103, Folder 22)
  - Elections Committee, 1958 (Box 103, Folder 23)
  - ASUA Publicity Committee, 1956-1958 (Box 103, Folder 24)
  - ASUA Social Events Committee (Nite Club, Night Club), 1959-1960 (Box 103, Folder 25)
  - ASUA; Mother’s and Dad’s Day, High School Senior Day, 1958-1960 (Box 103, Folder 26)
  - UA Student Religion Council, 1958-1960 (Box 103, Folder 27)
  - UA International Students Club, 1956-1959 (Box 103, Folder 28)
  - Pacific Student Presidents Association (PSPA), 1960 (Box 103, Folder 29)
  - Concerts, 1958-1960 (Box 103, Folder 30)
  - Board of Control, 1956-1957 (Box 103, Folder 31)
  - Board of Control, 1957-1958 (Box 103, Folder 32)
  - Board of Control, 1958-1959 (Box 103, Folder 33)
  - Board of Control, 1959-1960 (Box 103, Folder 34)
  - ASUA Student Insurance Program, 1960 (Box 103, Folder 35)
  - Office of the Vice President (Dr. Robert L. Nugent), 1957-1959 (Box 103, Folder 36)
  - Mom and Dad’s Day, 1957-1960 (Box 103, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence; ASUA, 1958-1960 (Box 103, Folder 38)